Translated by Releska
To me, it's always the same as the dream I've made
But there's always a moment when it's with you
Come on, come on, come on
There's a person who can make me laugh a little
So you're happy, but I don't want to cry for you
I'm just laughing at you
The time when the light shines
There will be a smile on your lips
You and you, you and you
If you love me,
I'll be with you in the middle of the heart
I don't want to be with you
I'm not a good boy
If I had taken the time machine
I would have been in a bad mood
We were told that we were going to live in a strange world
How will this happen?
A family of friends and friends
Do you really want to see me?
What are you doing?
I thought you were not looking at me
I'm not looking at you
I have become capable of living the world
And God has organization
I become capable of living the world
God
God has created me
Is this still the dream?
This is my prayer
Sorry it's about getting angry and children
What do you want to do?
What?
I'm going to make a joke with you!
Oh!
Oh, Tokagiya-san!
I didn't expect you to be here!
What's the matter?
I told my mom that I wanted to eat too.
Oh, I see.
What's the next?
I don't need to go back.
Oh, no!
I don't want to go back!
That was a joke!
Thank you!
If there was something bad,
I told my mom that I wanted to eat too.
Muka-muka-chan!
If there's something bad,
I'll eat too.
Beed!
Muka-muka!
Bye-bye!
Itadakimasu!
Komachi!
What?
I won't do that!
I won't!
I see.
It's a powerful weapon.
If you make this kind of weapon,
you can make it right away.
If you want to make it right away,
Can you see the TV?
It's impossible.
Even if the TV is on,
the power will come out.
Well...
The power is...
Of course, thank you very much.
What do you think about this machine?
Yes, yes, yes.
You can return to the original world someday.
Do you understand?
I see.
Actually, when I was working on this world,
I was able to imagine
how it would look like in a time machine.
how it would look like in that time.
That kind of power
would make you get in a machine.
The kind of power
I see.
I was able to imagine
how it would look when I get in a machine.
I see.
So how can I get in a machine?
Thank you very much.
I see.
I don't want to lose you.
Hey, Dad!
Oh!
There was a beautiful lake in the forest.
There was a lot of water.
Oh, right.
Now, the water's surface is gone.
I'll put this in the water.
I did it!
I didn't do the ice-money for a long time.
I didn't do that, but I can do it!
Oh, that's a lot of fun!
No one can stop me.
Everyone, let's eat.
Come in.
I've been waiting for you.
What are you doing today?
I'm going to have a meal.
Is that okay?
What?
I feel like I haven't come to the world for a long time.
Let's go.
It's because we're friends.
We're not friends anymore.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Yes, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
It's the most surprising thing in this world.
It's like a family of a family.
Really?
5.
The old man is going to die.
What?
What's going on?
The old man?
The old man is always there.
The old man's child is a rocker.
No, no.
Look, the old man is going to die.
Oh, I'm going to die.
The old man is going to die.
Oh, no, no.
This is it.
It's a rock and roll party.
Yay!
Oh, wait a minute.
Let's go home.
What?
It's falling.
Yay!
Thank you.
If you catch a cold, you'll die.
What?
It's not a big deal.
I'm going to go home because the old man is going to die.
I'm going to go home because I'm going to die.
The old man is going to die.
What happened to the old man?
He's going with the old man.
That's right.
I'm going to go home because I'm going to die.
The old man is going to die.
That's right.
I'm going to go home.
Well, I'm going to go home because I'm going to die.
It's no good.
This is my job right now.
I want to go home.
I thought it was our family.
But...
The problem is, it feels like it's our family.
Is it happiness in our house?
Is it happiness in our classroom?
It's a big deal.
Whatever you do...
...if you have this feeling...
If you can't meet with anyone at the same time with me...
then I wouldn't tell you what to do.
On a day like this
Yeah!
I'm an adult!
You're an adult, aren't you?
No, not at all.
I'm human, and you're the strength of a baby.
If I think about it, I can ask for a favor.
Where can I ask for a favor of my mom.
I'm so happy to see you again.
Hey, Muka-muka...
What are you saying?
What are you thinking about?
You're the one who's good at it.
Oh, what is it?
You're the one who's bad at it.
I'm not bad at it.
I'm just happy.
You're not bad at it.
What are you thinking about?
I'm so scared!
Ah! I'm scared!
I'm scared!
Oh, I'm so scared!
Oh, the other side?
The professor and...
Where did he go?
Huh? Is that okay?
Yeah, I made it!
I decided to give you the skills of the other side!
But I'm not the real mother of the other side!
Oh, I'm not the real mother of the other side!
Did you do the research?
Yeah!
Even if you don't worry, you'll come back right away!
I don't think I'll ever come back!
That's right!
I'm going to make the train!
I'm going to make the train too!
I need to work hard!
I won't do that!
I'll do my best!
I'm not playing around 3 people!
What do you two do?
10 people?
Where is my bus?
I'll try!
I'll work slowly after a while!
What?!
It's so heavy, I wonder?
Is it real?
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Who is this?!
It's a pretty big dog.
Whoa!
It's a turtle!
Here's where it is!
I can't run away from the door.
Let's go inside with us!
No, no, no.
I'm not going to sleep.
It's okay.
I'll sleep in the middle of the night.
I don't know what to do.
I'm not going to sleep!
I'm not going to sleep.
What?
What? What?
It's Aizu!
Aizu, Sampe.
Akira, come here.
Don't come home early.
I'm not happy with the other half.
It's the same classroom.
Oliver.
Food and coffee.
Hello, Mr. Dozuka.
I've said that I'm on a mission.
Shhh...
Nobody is there!
No way!
Kaka...
I think the neighbors are crying...
Say hi.
This door has been locked up in the eggway.
This door has been locked down in the eggway.
What's going on?
What do I do now?
Gokun
Can't sleep?
Dad?
I came here to study and I'm not sleepy.
That's right. Everyone seems to be in a hurry.
Everyone is doing their best to be in a hurry.
It's a peaceful time.
Is it a peaceful time?
I don't want to give you any answers.
If you come, you'll find a solution naturally.
But it might not be possible to come back.
Do you want me to come back to you?
That's good.
If you don't forget your feelings now, you'll come back.
Now, please.
If you want to go tomorrow, you can go.
Yes.
Good morning.
Let's go to Mr. Ranko's place.
Yes, Mr. Ranko.
What are you doing?
Let's go to Mr. Ranko's place.
Do you want me to come back?
Yes.
Mr. Ranko's place is here.
It's a peaceful time.
It's not a peaceful time.
I'm going to play.
I'm going to play with Mr. Ranko's place.
I'm doing well.
I'm going to play.
I want you to play with Mr. Ranko's place.
What are you doing?
I'm going to play with Mr. Ranko's place.
That's not scary.
Mr. Ranko's place is here.
I'm scared.
I'm going to die!
Help me!
I'm going to die too!
You're going to die too, aren't you?
I'm going to die!
If you think about it, you'll get a chance to die.
I want you to die!
But I'm glad!
I won't let anyone get away from me anymore!
I'm already dead.
It's like I'm going to die.
What the hell?
You're going to die too!
Hey! What do you want to die of?
I'm going to die soon.
No, no!
You'll have to listen to the next one!
And you're the best!
You can do it!
The third one is the best!
And the third one is the best!
Translated by Releska
It's a horrible day.
The day when I was in a bitter space.
I smiled a little and laughed at it.
Air, night, night.
Suddenly I was like a zombie.
I thought it'd be a bad weather.
It's the be by heart
Say, say, say, say, say, say
Sound.
Ski, superiority, squeezed!
Sound
Rise all around
It's fun, lie
Show us.